<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyle on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/lifestyle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyle on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:00:00 -0857</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Pace</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/the-importance-of-pace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:00:00 -0857</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/the-importance-of-pace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am starting to recognize the importance of pace. Growing up we&amp;rsquo;ve all heard the story of the tortise and the hare - short bursts vs. slow but continual effort. This reconition of pace dosen&amp;rsquo;t live on either of the extremes, but is rather somewhere in the middle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the last two weeks I have been working on building a backyard shed, something that I have been planning for and anticipating for a long time. I started with the foundation, prepping that, adding pest prevention, ensuring stability for longevity but I was only able to work for an hour or two at a time. Today I unexpectedly had some flexibility with work and was able to get a solid 4 hours at one time to make some major headway. This evening after dinner and putting Shae down, I headed out to maximize the last hour of sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The eternal struggle of analog vs digital</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/analog-vs-digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/analog-vs-digital/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have this eternal struggle with analog vs digital. I love trying out new products and have bounced from one tool to the next when it comes to life organization and note taking. Add in the complexity of collaboration and syncing up which tools to use with which person and it can be a real problem. On the flip side I have been using &lt;a href=&#34;https://fieldnotesbrand.com/&#34;&gt;Field Notes&lt;/a&gt; bookelts for as long as I can remember and recently I have been crushing on a number of Japaneese stationary products. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I will ever go fully analog or fully digital but therein lies the problem of how to keep things organized and what systems to put in place to keep the two methods talking to oneanother.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
